I'm glad to see you.
Please.
THE TWINS
Last will and testament of
Dr. Nawal Marwan.
Opening of the will to
her two children,
Simon Marwan and Jeanne Marwan.
"In accordance with the will,
regulations and rights of
Nawal Marwan,
the notary, Jean Lebel,
is named executor."
Hmm ... I must tell you here
that it was your mother's decision.
I was personally against
it, but she insisted.
You know ...
... your mother was more
than an employee.
To my late wife and me
you felt more like part
of our family, so ...
I could not refuse.
Hum!
"All my assets are to be
shared between the twins,
Jeanne and Simon Marwan."
"The money is to be equitably
shared"
"My furniture distributed by
mutual agreement."
"Burial"
"Notary Jean Lebel will
bury me without a coffin, naked
and without prayers."
"My face turned towards the ground,
my back against the world."
"Tombstone and Epitaph"
"No headstone is to be
placed on my grave
and my name engraved nowhere."
"No epitaph is deserved for those
who do not keep their promises."
"To Jeanne and Simon"
"Childhood is like a knife
stuck in the throat
which cannot be removed easily."
"Jeanne, notary Lebel will
hand you an envelope."
"This envelope is for your father."
"Find him
and hand him the envelope."
"Simon, the notary will
hand you an envelope."
I've heard enough.
Oh ... but it's not finished.
Continue.
"Simon, the notary will
hand you an envelope."
"This envelope is for your brother."
"Find him and hand it to him."
"When these envelopes
have been handed
to their addressees, a
letter will be given to you."
"When the silence is broken,
and the promise kept
a stone may be placed
on my grave
and my name engraved on
the stone."
I admit it's a bit strange.
Is there stuff to sign?
No, not today.
OK.
Thank you, Jean.
- Shall we?
- Wait.
You know, the history
of our father.
You know, we have no brother.
Why did you let her write this?
I understand your surprise.
It's ... it's very surprising.
Stop pretending to be innocent!
We know that we speak of, there is
nothing surprising in this.
We did not make these
things up, Simon...
They are part of a will.
There's that, too.
Well, this morning your mother
gave us something rather special.
We'll sleep on it, then ...
We'll meet again, huh?
I'll wait outside.
Thank you, Jean.
Sit down, Simon.
Look, Jean ...
your secretary, she loved
working for you.
She did this well all her
life, congratulations.
Your secretary, however, was also
my mother.
Then her job as a mother,
that's another story.
Simon ...
You can bury your secretary
in any way you wish.
But my mother, I want her
buried in the normal way.
For once in your fucking life
make it something normal.
This is not negotiable.
Take your time.
And come see me when Simon
has calmed down.
I know it's very unusual, but ...
your mother was not crazy, Jeanne.
We have a large family now.
She spoke of a traitor?
In a big family, there's always a dog.
How long will it be before we
find the traitor?
Fucking crazy woman!
I'll fix that with Jean.
Fix what?
We'll give her a
normal funeral.
We'll take care of her, then
I'll take care of you.
Where are you going?
You bury her any way you like!
Oh, stop!
You feel guilty because
you were not there
when she died.
You feel guilty because
you were there
when she had her accident.
You need to stop you feeling
guilty for everything!
I am not feeling guilty
about anything.
Do you realize the significance of
what he just read?
Well, she's gone!
It's over, I'm at peace!
I have fucking peace!
I'm at peace now.
Yes, I see.
Mathematics as you
have known so far
have aimed to achieve a precise
and definitive response
to precise and definitive problems.
Now, you are about to enter into
entirely different adventure.
The subject will be
intractable problems
that will always lead
to other problems just
as intractable.
People around you will
repeatedly insist
that what you are doing is
hopeless.
You'll have no argument
to defend yourself,
because they will be of an
overwelming complexity.
Welcome to pure mathematics,
the land of loneliness.
This is my assistant,
Miss Jeanne Marwan.
Hello!
We will start with the conjecture
of Syracuse.
What does your intuition
tell you?
Your intuition is always right.
That's why you got potential
to becoming a real mathematician.
But over there, you'll need help.
Do you have any family there?
- Contacts?
- It's ridiculous, Niv.
You've come to learn that
a) your father is alive;
and b) you have another brother.
This is ridiculous
What is ridiculous to question
the inevitable.
You need to know.
Otherwise, your mind
will never be at peace.
And peace of mind has nothing to
do with pure mathematics.
You need a starting point.
My father died during
the war in Daresh.
That's the unknown variable
in the equation.
You never start with the
unknown variable.
My mother used to speak about
a village
called Der Om, in Fouad.
She graduated in French
at the University of Daresh.
If she studied, there is hope.
Said Haidar.
You'll go knock on the
door Said Haidar
an old friend of mine who
teaches at Daresh.
You can trust him.
What are you doing?
Mom! Are you Okay?
Madam, that's my towel, please.
Mom?
Mom!
What happened?
Where's Jeanne?
Mom?
Does she suffer from migraines?
No.
- Memory loss?
- No.
Loss of balance?
No.
Absent-minded?
She's always absent.
No, she was never absent.
Wahab, come.
Just get out of my sister's way.
Son of refugees, where do you
think you're going?
Nicolas, stop!
Go back to your country.
Wahab!
We'll leave your hide
in your camps, believe me.
Give me.
- I want to kill her.
- It's mine to do.
You have sullied the
family honor.
- Enough!
Go home!
Outside.
What have you done!
You have humilliated us!
You have sullied the
name of our family!
Why God have you plunged
us in the dark?
My God, what have you done?
Why did you do that?
What will I do with you!
You want me to kill you?
I'm pregnant, grandma.
- My God, everything is black.
Why?
Why have you done this?
Do I have to kill you?
What will I do with you?
Come.
Eat if you want your
child safe.
Listen to me.
There's nothing here for you.
I'll help after the birth.
I want you to go away.
You'll go to live with
your uncle Charbel.
There, you'll go to school.
To learn to read,
to learn to think
out of this misery.
Promise me and I'll help you.
Promise me you'll go to school.
I promise you, grandmother.
I promise.
Shh.
Look carefully at your mother.
You'll have to recognize her.
I'll find you one day.
I promise you, my heart.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Come on, it's time
for you to go.
I feel that something terrible
is coming ...
One day I'll find you, my son.
I received a message
from my friend Niv Cohen
but I can't help you
because at the time,
I taught
History of Mathematics
in Paris.
Specifically, the period
where Euler had
succeeded
to give the first
formal mathematical resolution
to the problem of the seven bridges
of Konigsberg, yes.
Diderot defied the Court
saying:
"Gentlemen ..."
I-ft plus
Equals zero.
So, God exists!"
Niv, Niv, Niv ...
Hello! Do you speak French?
- Yes, of course!
- Can I help you?
Uh, yes, I am looking for someone
who would have known this woman.
She studied here maybe
35 years ago.
Are you kidding me?
I wasn't even born.
Well, you're in the wrong
place...
I'm not kidding.
I'm sure you know someone
who can help me.
I have come from far away.
Please. Her name is Nawal Marwan.
You are very kind.
I'm not nice, I want
to get rid of you.
Najat, that's me.
You have time to waste?
That tells me something.
She may have worked in the
campus newspaper.
It's been a long time.
People who leave usually
change identities.
It is striking nonetheless.
Your mother was photographed
in Kfar Ryat.
Look here.
This is a sign of Kfar Ryat.
It is a prison in the south.
You do not know Kfar Ryat?
- No.
You're definitely not from
here.
You don't know the South.
If the international community
does not intervene now
The refugees in overcrowded
camps at the border ...will be
massacred.
She has arrived.
OK.
We, the students, are oppose
against the Nationalist Party
that are trying to evict the refugees
across the borders.
The National Party supports
militias of the Christian right,
who make open threats against
the refugees.
In the South, the refugees
are now armed.
And have the support
of much of the country's Muslim
population.
But you ...you're a Christian.
We are for peace.
Religion has nothing
to do with it.
Nawal!
Put the radio!
They've come to close
the University!
The Nationalists have
closed the campus!
Nawal, come back.
Stay here.
Uncle Charbel, the Nationalists
are closing the campus!
There will be clashes.
Stay with me.
There is shooting outside ...
To the table, girls!
Mom, they're attacking
the university!
It's not a reason not to eat!
Aioua?
Christian villages were attacked
in the South this morning.
May God protect us!
That's why they closed
the university.
In short time, it will
explode here as well.
We'll go to the mountain
until it calms down.
For how long?
We start tomorrow.
The rest of the family
is already there.
And the school?
Anyway, the school will close.
Only God knows how long.
And Le Journal?
Don't be afraid.
Le Journal can survive without
us for a while.
But ideas only survive if someone
is there to defend them!
Exactly, Rafqa.
Exactly.
There are only two orphanages
in the region.
I will join you soon.
You will not go there now!
You had promised Grandma you
would finish your studies.
You heard your father.
It's going to explode across the country
if they attack the camps.
The studies are finished.
I think of him every day.
That's my child.
I want to find him alive.
I'm going to fetch
water from Shadia.
Hurry, Nawal.
- Your name?
- Nawal.
- Nawal what?
- Nawal Marwan.
Where are you going?
South.
What for?
To meet my husband.
Wahab.
You have only daughters?
The older boys are in Kfar
Kout.
You should go with us.
Kfar Kout was attacked
yesterday.
Looking for the orphanage.
You know where is it?
There.
The children?
Where are the children?
You should speak with those
who were there.
The muslim villagers fled
to the camp Deressa.
They fear reprisals will come.
The children may be with them.
Chamseddine and his men killed all the
Christians to avenge the refugees.
Perhaps the children are in Deressa.
Can you take me to the camp in Deressa?
I am a Christian.
My daughter! My daughter!
Mom!
Hi, Simon, it's me!
I am in Mama's village.
I wish you were here with me.
Listen.
Oh, I'm sorry, I do not understand.
I told you never to come here again!
Hello!
Souha?
Ahmed loves you!
I told you not to say that again!
Hello.
Can I help you?
Does anyone speak French
or English?
Where's Sami?
Marhaba!
Hello!
(Arabic)
Uh, Jeanne.
Jeanne.
Uh ...
Thank you.
- You speak French?
- Yes, hello!
Hello.
My name is Samia.
I am Jeanne Marwan.
Thank you for helping me.
Marwan?
There are many Marwans here.
Really?
Well, I'm from Canada.
I'm looking for Souha.
She is Souha.
She is my great-grandmother.
- Oh! Marhaba!
- Marhaba.
The people in the corner shop
told me to come see you.
I am looking for my father.
His name is Wahab.
Uh ...My mother's name
is Nawal Marwan.
She was born here.
We do not know her.
Of course you know her.
The Marwan family was struck with
shame.
When the war came.
Uh, I'm looking for Wahab.
She does not know Wahab.
I can not help you.
Sorry, I'm tired.
If you're Nawal Marwan daughter,
you're not welcome here.
Go home.
She is looking for her father,
but she doesn't know
who is her mother.
I arrived at the end of the massacre
in the Deressa refugee camp.
Everything was burning.
I looked for my son amid
waves of blood.
I was disheartened by what I saw
and heard.
You claim to be against
our enemy.
That does not make you our friend.
Chamseddine. why would
he trust you?
My son's father was
a refugee from Deressa.
My son has been swallowed
by the war.
I have nothing to lose.
My hatred is great toward
the Nationalists.
This is not what you wrote
in Charbel's journal.
My uncle Charbel thought to encourage
peace with words and books.
I believed that.
Life has taught me
something else.
What are you going to do now?
Teach the enemy what
life has taught me.
That's goog. That's good.
You've just forgotten it. Let's go.
So in French?
I ... I am much better, Dad.
They say "a lot" or "best"
but never both at the same
time, my darling.
I want my son to learn to speak
several languages.
I want him to understand others
without an intermediary.
How are you, Nawal?
It's Nouchine.
Good evening, Nouchine.
How's your mother?
My mother is very well.
10:00 o'clock tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
Marhaba.
Hello, beautiful.
Good morning.
Then you will be going out
with us on Thursday?
No.
Friday?
Saturday?
No.
We are patient!
Me too.
Never forget:
"Always" is "always".
Fucking bitch.
The prison at Kfar
Ryat was comdemmed in
several reports by Amnesty
International.
Here is the women's section.
The cells are larger.
Some prisoners remained
there up to 15 years.
- It has existed since when?
- At the time of the massacres.
Just after the war began.
They have 600 political
prisoners jailed.
You can come in, eh?
I'll take a picture.
You know this woman?
No.
She was imprisoned here.
I don't know her.
It was a really long time
ago, you know? I...
Maybe you know someone
who worked here.
Hello.
I'm looking for Harrsa Fahim.
I am the school janitor.
Yes, but before, what were you?
Before, hum!
That was before I became the
school janitor.
It's been a long time since I'm
caretaker of the school.
You know this woman?
She was in Kfar Ryat.
I am a school janitor.
Bess! That's all.
I am looking for someone
who knew her.
Someone who could
tell me about her.
This is my mother.
This is the woman who sings.
Number 72.
It was she who murdered the
militia leader
of the christian right.
They made her pay dearly.
Very, very dearly.
Fifteen years.
They used to call her the
woman who sings
because she sang all the time.
Han, you are sure it's her?
I spent 13 years as a watchman.
Have you ever spent 13 years
overseeing someone?
They did everything
to make her break.
In the end, she was
still standing,
She looked ...
Ah! Never seen anything like it.
She never broke.
It was exasperating.
And then they sent Abu Tarek.
Who's that?
Abu Tarek...
You know, sometimes it's better
not to know everything.
Sir, I live with it anyway.
Continue.
Abu Tarek...
Abu Tarek was a investigation
specialist.
He raped her repeatedly
to break her before being
released.
To stop her from singing.
Eventually she became pregnant.
It was like that.
I'll never forget it.
Number 72 pregnant by Abu Tarek.
They waited ...
for her to give birth in prison
then they let her go.
The child?
Did you see the child?
There was a doctor who came
sometimes.
I think he's crazy.
Others say he has a restaurant
in Tel Aviv ...
That's bullshit.
He went mad and died.
His nurse, I know her.
She lives in Daresh.
In Daresh?
Listen, Simon, I'm calling you!
I'm calling you, no, shut up, OK?
Shut your mouth!
Mom, she was in prison.
Simon, mom, she ...
Mom, she was raped.
Our brother, she had him in prison.
I need you here.
THE WOMAN THAT SINGS
This, Simon, are notary Amyott
contracts
from 1868 to 1892.
His son took over, Édouard,
until 1925.
All the contracts are hand-written.
My grandfather, Charles,
my father, Henry.
And me.
Yeah, well, it stops there
because as you know,
I am the last of the Lebel.
I'll show you the
will of a man ...
... which took several lives.
His heirs have discovered
he had three wives, all
at the same time.
One here, one in Miami,
and another in Honduras,
where he did business.
No, no ...he not longer has
three children in the file there, no
There are eight.
That is sport, my man.
Look. Hum!
Death is never the
end of a story.
There are still traces.
If you want to find
your brother,
you'll have to go back into
your mother's past.
Jean, I'm going to fetch my
sister, that's all.
I'll take care of that.
Two, three small matters
to take care,
then it will take no time.
Well, get your business ready
we should go in ...
My passport ...
"We"? Don't you worry that
you already done enough already
Exactly, this is not the
time to let you down.
Make a man out of you, Simon.
I know that you need me.
We'll get it, then come back.
I promise.
Then, promise, Mr. Marwan,
a notary is on the order
of the sacred.
Sing now.
Gently, gently.
He is coming out.
We can see the head.
Push, push.
Go, girl.
The first came out.
Rest now ...
I'm proud of you.
Get ready for the second.
Stop.
What are you doing?
You are going to dump them in the
river as usual.
- It's dangerous.
- No.
You've done your duty.
Throw them in the river.
I want to take care of them.
These are the children of
the woman who sings.
Oh, this country is a war
zone after another, eh!
It's not complicated.
If the notary had existed
at the time of Noah,
we would not be here.
We need only to find the
original contracts.
That's up to you, that's up to you.
And a right of passage there.
And we talk more about it.
Everyone would be happy.
Notaries have existed
only in the last 1,000 years, Simon.
That's the problem.
I should have been here from
the beginning.
Thank you again for your
help, Me Maddad.
The pleasure is all
mine, my dear fellow.
I have the result
that you have requested
via email.
Simon my file on
the seat beside you.
Could you give it to
Lebel, please?
You are very nice, but the
delay and everything ...
I think I'll wait until later.
But I'll summarize.
For the father, it is
rather difficult
because I can not find
the death certificate.
For the brother ...
Excuse me, but what
are we talking about here?
I asked for help, Simon.
Me Maddad kindly gave us a hand
to speed things up.
I told you, Jean,
we came for Jeanne.
Your sister is the one person
in your family
easiest to find.
I'm so glad you're here.
Me too.
OK, that's the nurse's name.
which helped your mother give birth
in prison.
We can go today.
Jeanne, that's enough.
No, you shut up, then follow me.
It's your job to find our
brother, not mine!
Then, if you don't do it for
her or for you,
the, do it for me!
She is at the American hospital.
I'm glad you're here, Jean.
Me too, my owl, me too.
If she is sleeping, you must return
later.
Ms. Maika?
Lebel, Jeanne Marwan,
Simon Marwan.
Bonjour, Madame!
Thank you for having us.
We seek someone you know.
Nawal Marwan, do you know her?
You worked in the Kfar Ryat prison
as a nurse?
She says she knows your mom.
You helped our mother
give birth in prison?
Yes.
Madame, the child we seek is Nawal
Marwan's son that was born in prison.
Can you help us?
She worked in the prison
of Kfar Ryat.
She assisted her
during childbirth.
She gathered the children.
Then she gave them back
to the woman who sings
when she got out of prison.
Nawal Marwan gave
birth to twins.
Hush, hush, hush.
You really know the
woman who sings?
You don't know what
it means to me.
Nawal Marwan worked for me
as a secretary for 18 years.
My wife and I, we had
taken a liking
to her and her children.
But I confess that I
didn't really know her till the end.
- Ready?
- Ready.
Hmm ...
Me Maddadi has conducted an
investigation, at my request,
to track your brother
and your father.
For the father, Abu Tarek,
I still have not found
a death certificate.
The country has a lot
of certificates missing.
He could have gone abroad.
That's what happened with
this kind of characters.
They are dead or have disappeared.
You have to see.
Maybe it's better that way.
For the brother ...
your client, Ms. Nawal Marwan,
comes from the village
of Der Om.
She gave the child to a midwife
who's named Elham
who herself returned it to
the orphanage in Kfar Kout
in May 1970.
The main task was to
trace the registry records.
Many documents have been
lost in the war.
But I found the records
which were recovered and donated
by the Sisters of Charity
to the National Archives.
In May 1970, the midwife at
Der Om, Elham
filed a petition for adoption
of a male child.
This is the only boy in the
orphanage filed in that month.
Look.
It was registered under
the name Nihad.
The dates match.
That's him.
Ha! It's your brother! Nihad.
Orphanage Kfar Kout,
Nihad May.
It's his name in the registry.
Nihad from the month of May.
They gave him a temporary name
with the month of arrival.
There was no adoption
during that period.
It was the beginning of the war.
The orphanage was destroyed
four years later.
We must ask those that destroyed
the orphanage in Kfar Kout
to know what happened
to the children.
Between you and me, with what
happened in the region ...
there is not much hope.
They are probably also dead.
I'm not saying they're dead.
I say we lost track of them.
They are both dead.
We open the envelopes,
that's it, then.
That I will not allow, Simon.
This kind of thing is sacred.
Luckily, I have a history.
Excuse me.
It is still worth exploring.
But it is a little radical.
The warlord
that demolished the orphanage
at that time is still alive.
And he may know what happened
to Nihad's children and where
they went.
It's already been an eternity.
You must understand
that during this period there were
a series of reprisals
which fit one another in
a sort of inexorable logic,
A warlord is exactly
the type of man who
has a long memory.
And he will remember, believe me.
Wallat Chamseddine,
is his name.
We can find him here?
If we don't find him, he
will find us.
But we can try something.
Would you like tea, Mr. Marwan?
It's your turn.
You will go
to the Deressa refugee camp.
You will come to tea
anywhere in the camp
with the person that invite you.
And you say you are the son
of the woman who sings
and are looking Nihad May.
You can not go there alone.
I'll find someone
to accompany you.
Welcome to Deressa.
Ha! Ha! You know where you
are going, Simon?
I know.
How are you?
In the name of God, you've grown!
I have finished my engineering studies.
I cannot find work, so I'm
a taxi driver now.
What brings you here?
I am with some foreign visitors, who
asked me to bring them here.
Welcome, come.
No, thank you, we're
in a hurry.
Please, come.
He is inviting us to tea.
Oh, good!
Uh, I wonder why you have
come to Deressa.
I am looking for someone
named Nihad de Mai.
He does not know Nihad de Mai.
He asks me what are your names.
My mother comes from the village
of Der de Om, in the South.
My mother is the woman who sings.
Yes, that's fine. Done.
Wait for what?
- Sarwan Marwan?
- Yes.
We are here to offer help.
You will be back in an hour.
Can I tell my sister?
No, you'll be back in
an hour, I promise.
I'll put on a shirt, just a second.
He will call.
He's going to go.
Ok! Do not worry, you can follow.
Ah, I told you: the South,
a spark and it exploded.
Oh, okay.
You have been luck with us,
we'll help in our own way.
You must leave the country.
It'll be easier.
We will find you a house and a job.
I want your life to be better.
We have many contacts
in America.
You gotta go with your children.
I know they are alive.
Take them with you.
The children will help
you, you'll see.
You cannot ask me.
Your children are our
children, Nawal.
Your family is our family.
Trust me.
I'll help you.
I'm here for you and
your children.
Hello, Sarwan.
Excuse my introduction, but
it is for your protection.
They call me Wallat Chamseddine.
Tell me, what can I do to
help, Sarwan Marwan?
You knew my mother.
They say she worked for me.
What can I do to help?
I am looking for a
man named Nihad de Mai.
Why you are looking for Nihad de Mai?
He's my brother.
My mother asked me to find him.
And how can you prove that
Nihad de Mai is the son
of Nawal Marwan?
My brother was
placed for adoption
at the Kfar Kout orphanage.
We found the registry with
the original file.
The dates ... Everything fits.
Nihad de Mai is my brother.
Me and my friends, we attacked
the christian village at Kfar Kout ...
In response to attacks
that our brothers, the refugees,
were victims of.
There was an orphanage
in Kfar Kout.
I saved the children.
I took them with us.
And Nihad was among them.
We have trained and prepared
them so that they can fight
alongside us.
Nihad, he had a gift.
He was at unique.
And soon it became a
formidable fencer.
But he wanted to
find her mother.
He sought her for a long time.
Nihad, I do not know what
he saw or heard.
He started ...
a crazy war.
He came to see me, he
wanted to be a martyr
so that his mother should see
his picture everywhere
on the walls around the country.
But I refused.
He went back to Daresh.
He became a maverick,
one of the most dangerous  in the region.
A real machine.
He pulls on everyone.
And then there was the
enemy invasion.
And one morning ...
They captured Nihad.
He killed seven gunmen.
They did not killed them.
They captured him
and sent him to the prison
in Kfar Ryat.
He has been in prison?
Yes.
He is the executioner.
He worked with my father?
- No, he did not work
with Abu Tarek, your father.
- Are you okay?
One plus one ...
that makes two.
What?
One plus one makes two.
You can not make one.
Hey, you have a fever.
Jeanne?
One plus one, does it make one?
Are there are empty seats, no.
Oh, move ahead if you want.
Can I help you, ma'am?
Excuse me.
By becoming a hangman
your brother has changed
its name.
He became Abu Tarek.
Nihad de Mai is Abu Tarek.
We know that he now lives in Canada
under a new identity.
Nihad Harmanni.
Mr. Harmanni?
Yes?
This is for you.
My hand is shaking while
I am writing this.
I recognized you.
But you didn't.
It's a wonderful miracle.
I'm your number 72.
This letter will be delivered
by our children.
You will not recognize them
because they are beautiful,
but they know who you are.
Through them, I want to tell you
you're still alive.
But soon, you'll be quiet.
I know.
Because silence is
all to the truth.
Signed: The whore 72.
I speak to my son.
I am not talking to
the executioner.
Whatever happens, I will
always love you.
That's the promise I made you
at birth, my son.
Whatever happens, I will
always love you.
I've searched my whole life.
I found you.
You, you could not recognize me.
You have your tattoo
on the right heel.
I've seen it.
I recognized you.
And I found you beautiful.
I'll remember you with all the
sweetness of the world, my love.
Console yourself because nothing
is more beautiful
than being together.
You were born of love.
Your brother and your sister
were also born of love.
Nothing is more beautiful
than to be together.
Your mother, Nawal Marwan.
Prisoner number 72.
"When these envelopes
have been handed
"to the addressee,
"You will be given a letter."
"The silence will be broken,
"a promise kept,
"A stone may then be placed
on my grave,
and my name engraved on
the stone facing the sun."
My love ...
Where did your story begin?
When you were born?
Then she starts in horror.
At the birth of your father?
Then she begins a
great love story.
I say that your story
begins with a promise
that will break
the thread of anger.
Thanks to you, today I finally
managed to do it.
The thread is broken.
And I can finally take
the time to rock you in my arms...
and softly sing you a lullaby
to comfort you.
Nothing is more beautiful
than to be together.
I love you.
Your mother, Nawal.