Scarytorrent.com.br
translation and sync: saredes
In 2014, the last
skeptics are silent.
The climate disaster is worse than imagined.
Antarctic Ice
will be gone within a decade.
Alpine glaciers disappear.
The consequences are unclear,
but we know one thing.
Life on Earth will change forever.
We will change.
Janek?
Can you please hold the dog?
Janek. Janek.
Yes
Base Climate Research Glazius -
3500m Crew: 3 scientists, 1 coach, 1 dog
Fucking idiots.
Honestly, Harald, is intolerable,
something.
Really?
Thank you. And good morning.
Harald .
-Good morning.
What?
The measuring station 3
does not transmit more data.
No kidding.
And what will you do now?
Well, the problem is in the transformer again.
I'll look when my head.
So, will you? When?
While we are no climatic data, Janek?
For that you need
climate data?
Not collecting stones?
But the stones are my
research and for which
is very interesting to see how the weather is today.
Oh yes, but basically it
is right, or what?
Then collect stones?
I am not a mineralogist, I collect rocks?
Janek, how long will
need to fix this?
Tomorrow, when the minister comes,
everything should work again.
I do not know. Three hours, when the transformer is
.
Tinni.
What?
Now what?
What? Let's eat.
Come.
How long have you lived here?
Since the season is here, right?
Five years.
Why?
Why not?
Why not? Where should I start?
Oh, come on, Janek.
The work is only for a year.
An agreement for a second year
is very rare.
Extend  But four times?
Is not nothing nice here.
Must be a reason.
You need to be familiar with the station.
What they say is another story.
I do not know if it's true, but...
Do you remember a glaciologist who
been here three or three and a half years ago?
Tanja Monstatt.
Scientists come and go every few weeks.
You forget.
I understand.
Come, Tinni. Come on.
Hey, Tinni.
Stop there. Tinni.
Well, I thought you had it under control
.
Boy. What?
You're crazy, huh?
Maybe he was behind it.
What is this?
So what is it?
I think this is something organic.
I have to get a sample.
Stop. Get out.
What can be?
Tinni?
What? Huh?
What happened to you?
Damn.
Come . Come on.
Falk, Janek, please attend.
Why not respond?
We have a small problem. An injury.
Oh my God, what happened to Falk? Janek?
Is not so serious, do not panic.
Rates.
Oh, you lost your mind?
Now hold still.
You're bleeding in the head.
This is nothing.
Here, do it yourself.
What are you doing?
Tinni is injured.
What?
Is bad?
No, it's not so bad. Is not deep.
What happened?
I do not know. He struggled with something.
In the cave? With what?
Probably a fox with rabies.
A fox?
'll Be okay. Yes
This was in defrost?
What is this?
Is organic?
Definitely.
Botanical Something?
I thought of it first.
Sometimes it happens that certain algae
glacial turn red, but...
These are not algae at
least none I've ever seen.
I would say yes, are organisms.
But none that is common.
Seems as if they were instances of
cells and disintegrate.
What?
They disintegrate. UV reaction,
I think, or contamination in the container.
I have to go necessarily bring
fresh samples. In a sterile container.
Janek, you take me?
Now?
Yes, now.
No, I'm not going anywhere
more today.
Will soon be night and has a
fox with rabies there.
And you're drunk.
Janek, are you okay?
No, my head hurts.
Shit.
Can a concussion?
Oh, nonsense.
He needs to come back.
No matter what. Today it will not take
anyone anywhere.
Then you come with me.
No way.
It is very dangerous at night.
You'll have to go. I can not go alone,
and so the cells will disintegrate.
Stop. Today no one goes to the glacier
more. End of story.
Friends.
This incident we keep to ourselves, right?
Tomorrow, when the minister comes.
Bodicek will really bring other climbers?
It Bodicek  Minister.
What if I tell you what happened.
Janek, I understand you.
But.
's Really a good idea?
I do not think so. Listen,
will be as a friendly event.
The Mountaineers, the minister and us.
In the long term,
worth more when we play together.
The fox angrily
will play too?
Do not know if it has rabies.
Course has a healthy fox
does something.
That fox jumps over a dog?
Tell me he is vaccinated?
Course. It's okay.
We have to say to those who come tomorrow
. We must warn them.
We have to do something else.
Take something for the pain and go to sleep
.
Here.
What is this?
Morphine . Open your mouth.
Morphine?
This should act fast.
Do you feel anything?
No, what?
I can take too?
You?
Janek, now you will sleep.
Let's do better.
Janek?
Is Tanja.
Janek, are you there? Come on, please.
Tanja, are you?
I am. Surprise.
I thought, I'll
again to save the climate.
Wait.
Shit.
And if he talks about the
fox with rabies?
They will cancel the visit.
Now the fox is the last thing he's thinking
, trust me.
Tanja?
What are you doing here?
Where are you?
Now I'm working in the ministry.
Imagine  I'm on the team
Department of Climate.
Tell me you would not have
to tell me earlier?
What? I was coming?
Yes, you came.
Why?
Because then I would leave.
You would pro hairdresser, or what?
Well, shave.
We leave tomorrow morning and spent over
Bullfinch Charte.
I look forward to tomorrow.
Why do not you take the
Passeierweg, is much shorter.
The path is very steep and
minister is not in such good shape.
Also,
distance is longer and gives better pictures.
I understand.
Well, until tomorrow.
Ok, see you tomorrow.
Shit.
Who's there?
Harald, I need the gun.
But be silent.
What?
Janek?
I'm here.
There is something there.
What is happening?
The fox is here. Be careful.
Your Face.
Looks like a beetle.
What?
Fast . Inside.
Where are you going?
What is he doing?
Must be a fox with rabies.
Janek, what are you doing?
Close the door.
I do not know.
She's totally deformed.
The torn face. Lock the door.
Because nobody goes out, is that clear?
Janek, calm down.
What you think you saw out there?
Is not paying attention?
There is something there.
Do something .
-I do not know what is.
Janek, this fox is not only angry,
is now deformed, or what?
Yes, that's it.
Janek,
out there is dark and you're totally confused.
I know what I saw, dammit.
Of course I believe in you, you believe you saw something
.
Hear me, you're the head
exhausted and sore.
E analgesics.
E alcohol.
We have to cancel the visit.
They can not come.
This is very dangerous. Where is
satellite phone, I have to call now.
So you will not see your ex?
Are you serious?
You see that? He wants to fight.
Janek, you're absolutely right.
The fox is a problem we have to solve
. But tomorrow. Look, who knows,
maybe you can handle until tomorrow
improve head, find him and kill him.
Or maybe he's already dead.
Shut up. Let Tinni.
Tinni?
Janek.
Sleep in my bed.
I sleep on the couch.
No
I'll sleep in my bed.
Come on.
Hey, all right?
Come here. Yes, it's okay. Come here.
Come, Janek. Come, I'll walk you
, yes?
Lock the door.
He belonged to a hunter.
Came back here.
They fell off the mountain together.
The hunter died instantly.
E Tinni,
it was located next to the corpse, the seriously injured.
We feed
refund and your health. Tanja and me.
He'll be excited tomorrow.
When you see her.
We'll see tomorrow. Come on.
Now go to sleep.
Monster.
Good day, Janek.
Good day.
Do you want a coffee?
What is he doing now?
Look at this?
Place here.
Ham with horseradish.
Looks delicious.
Feel free.
Stop.
This is so beautiful.
Should not take pictures before eating
? Where is Urs?
Urs Come, take a picture of us.
Come here.
Okay catching the food too?
Tanja, come on, please.
Pronto.
License.
Okay. Now we can.
Do you want an egg, Bertl?
Course.
Tanja, please let.
There is a small problem here.
I do not know if it's a good idea you see here
. We have a rabid animal here.
What? Again, I did not understand
.
A rabid animal.
As a rabid animal?
Could not be more accurate? What kind of animal?
Well, a fox...
probably a fox.
Probably a fox. Janek, you want
only prevent me from getting to you, right?
I do not want to stop you from doing anything.
Just wanted you to know.
The animal bit Tinni.
Janek, is this true?
Has a fox with rabies here.
Do what you want. Cambio.
Janek.
There is a problem at the station?
No. Everything in order.
They are waiting for us.
Can we?
It's coming.
E?
You warned the minister?
I've said what I meant.
They come.
I want to know what is happening with my
glacier.
Do you still want to go upstairs?
Absolutely.
Where is?
Are you sure this is the right place?
You see? Gone.
I told you yesterday that this would happen
.
But I was here.
You'll get samples?
This is enough.
We will return.
Are you crazy?
I will take a sample of the core hole.
Come on, let me do this.
I can do it alone.
But  hurry.
Right.
So I think it should take more
four hours. Even for beginners.
And we have untrained people here.
Definitely not.
Four hours, Bertl you think?
Including breaks?
Breaks? You want to take breaks?
No, I'm just asking.
Do not need breaks, right?
Luca Thank you, thank you.
So, you are also responsible for checking the body of
Bodicek?
What?
There is a problem, Luca?
No, it's alright.
Everything is in order.
A second, Tanja.
Irene.
The office received a report on the station.
There was an error, Dr. Monstatt discovered.
Could you please explain to us, Doctor?
Actually, it's not a mistake.
Several numbers are no longer current.
The glacier is shrinking much faster than we thought.
Even exponencialmente.O
which presents us with the question, why is it happening,
and worry because it proves that science has reached
the ceilings.
All predictions were wrong
even the worst.
We need something to hold.
This is new.
's Only vegetative reactions.
Do not worry.
He's dead.
How it stinks.
It stinks? That's all you can say?
It reeks of history of science.
Could someone please tell me what this is
?
I have no idea.
Something you have not seen yet?
Is a kind of animal
undiscovered?
What then?
I have a theory, but
is not scientific.
Bring it on, tell us.
First:
I believe in you, your
fox was deformed.
Here. The point I wanted to show you.
Because we need to take a picture.
It's hard to believe, but as a child,
there was snow everywhere.
The glacier extended down yonder.
All gone.
Incredible.
We have to take pictures here. Come on.
Now lets take a team photo
Department of Climate. Come on, Doctor.
What happened?
Oh, my God.
He marks on my neck?
Wait, you still have something...
is actually true. They are the same thing
, I can not believe it.
What is it?
They are the same as
bodies frozen in the glacier.
E?
I think the creature is a hybrid
a louse and a fox.
What?
How is this possible?
Seated.
I believe these organizations
are like little laboratories of genetics.
And I believe they need an incubator.
They pass through ingestion
as food for the body and use their DNA.
its DNA
all animals that are found in the stomach.
And combine them into a new species.
Completely random.
principle of trial and error.
According to evolutionary principle.
But as born?
I imagine that the body develops through
incubators.
The fox in the measuring station,
her belly had burst.
Exactly, and something like a
amniotic sac attached to it.
Imagine.
The fox takes water from the glacier
with microorganisms.
The fox, the largest omnivore
throughout the animal world,
eats a louse and a beetle.
stomach fox microorganisms absorb
the gene fox, louse and
Beetle and mix them.
Shortly after the fox-beetle and fox-
lice break out of your stomach.
How did that happen so fast
?
But that was just a few days ago.
And why  so great, how can a louse
be as large as a small dog?
Insects grow rapidly.
It can be assumed that all beings
mixed grow very quickly,
because the structure of the food chain, in
suggests genetic mixing in almost everyone.
One or more insects were incorporated.
Affecting one or more bugs.
Reaching its size shortly after.
And if an animal
've eaten these organisms
biting a human?
Or lick his blood?
The new hybrid will go into
your body through the blood.
If they are eaten or bitten
, the cycle continues.
Each mixture is possible.
Perhaps the legends of werewolves and mermaids
return to biological realities.
This may have happened.
Perhaps  Anubis, Egyptian god of the dead.
Actually,
was a human being with the head of a jackal.
Tanja, hello?
Any chance pass by
Passeierweg?
Why would we do that?
Because it is very dangerous to pass by Bullfinch Charte.
Dangerous? How so dangerous?
Janek,
can you tell me what is happening?
Tanja, I do not care how you do it.
I want to do it ASAP.
Please take the Passeierweg.
Why?
Just say it's a fox
angry, ok?
A fox with rabies.
Tanja, I know how that sounds...
But you are really in great danger.
Tanja?
Ok, I'll try.
Sorry.
Listen everyone.
What was that?
Just a hawk.
Listen, a fox was sighted
angry here.
Anger?
Never had an animal with rabies here.
Yes, but have you had an incident of attack
,
then we will move to
straight to the top path.
But it is significantly steeper.
Okay, but is much faster and will darken
soon.
Just because of a fox?
We are vaccinated.
And he's armed.
Luca, what do you think?
How long we win?
I do not know the terrain.
An hour at least, I think.
Minister,
I recommend changing the path.
Well, let's go.
If so, I do not care for
.
Okay, if you insist.
Janek, come on, please.
I've done it. We are now in
steeper path.
Okay, great.
That was Tinni?
Is he okay?
But why?
What's wrong with him?
I thought he was vaccinated?
I do not know. I have no idea.
Janek, you're not going to put him to sleep
, right?
Please do not do this, okay?
Wait until I come, like to see that.
Maybe he still has a chance.
Hurry.
Urs?
What?
I'm fine. I'm ok.
Are you sure?
Tanja, where were you?
Sorry. They were waiting for me?
Well, not really.
We have a case to the hospital here.
What is happening?
Maybe sunstroke.
's Okay, I just got a little dizzy
, it's okay.
Luca can take you to the hostel.
No, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yes I'm sure. Have
'll walk again.
Luca, help him.
Sure, I'll help you. Come on.
What? Why come sooner?
I told them to take Passeierweg.
Why?
Why? What do you think?
Is out there full of monsters
fox-bear-beetle.
Janek.
I'm going to meet them.
Wait a minute. Wait.
Wait a minute.
Janek, you talked about it?
Das mutations?
No, no one would believe me
.
Thank God. Thank God.
It's okay.
Janek? I mean that in no
should tell that to the minister.
We have to keep it a secret.
Janek, it is the greatest discovery
science since... forever.
We still know very little to go public.
The risks are endless.
Can cause mass panic, or worse.
Reporters who are
path should not know that.
You can be hundred percent sure that the
minister either.
This information is extremely confidential.
Janek. Can we pretend that nothing happened.
To gain time. To think about it.
At the moment, only talk fox.
They even know it. And when they were
, we went back to it again.
What do you think?
What do you say?
I say goodbye.
I go to them now and as they become
here in safety, they know everything.
You can not do this to us.
What?
Stop. Now.
Is irresponsible what you're doing. Shit
.
Our patient desperately need a break.
No, I do not. I need not pause.
Hey, look at yourself.
You look terrible. For the love of God.
Luca? Tanja?
The man needs a
break, I do not care about the fox.
Come here.
Okay. Only a break.
Looks terrible.
I feel better already.
I think I just had a
allergic reaction or something.
Let . We must move on.
But I just sit.
What was that? What was that?
Hey. Hey, calm down. Come on.
's Okay. Come on, breathe.
Breathe. Come on.
What happened?
What happened to you? Tell me.
's Okay.
's Okay. It's okay.
Down.
What is this?
Stay down.
Luca, shoot.
He was.
Is everything okay?
Luca.
Luca. We need to help Luca.
Tanja? Hello?
Get out of the way.
Janek.
Run, run.
-Tanja.
Come on, Janek.
Tanja, what happened?
Kissing the hand.
Kissing the hand of the Minister.
Ah, Mr. Krakauer.
I read everything.
I have...
many questions.
Oh, Mrs. Bodicek.
Get out of the way. Put it here.
Yes, lie down here.
Very slowly. Very slowly.
Urs? Urs?
Oh God, Urs is out there. Urs. Urs.
Urs. Urs. Oh God.
Calm. Calm.
Urs headed toward the valley.
Can you hear me? Calm.
Calm. Urs was toward the valley.
Can you hear me? The valley.
'll Be okay.
Janek, you can ask for help? Now.
Harald where the satellite phone?
And where are Falk and Birte?
They are out there.
Outside? Why are they out there?
They went to the glacier.
To the glacier?
Harald where the satellite phone?
At the measuring station.
At the measuring station?
Only for a few hours.
Only until tomorrow. Until
minister go.
Janek, we had no idea that such a thing would happen
. Believe me.
Truly had the best intentions.
We were afraid of discovery.
And you do something rash
and consequences.
Hey Janek, stop.
Can not ask for help because of them.
I can call for help.
I have a cell phone.
The cell has no signal here.
Need the satellite phone.
But Luca has.
Luca had.
Hold this.
Stop eating bananas, and crying.
They will return .
They will return soon.
And then explain everything.
And then we ask for help. Ok?
... Shhh... Now look at me. We're safe.
Everything will be fine.
Tinni.
Janek, no. No. Please do not Janek.
Okay, now tell me everything.
What exactly is this discovery?
Do not have the key.
What?
And what do you mean?
Do not get mad. Janek has the key.
Falk. You do not have a spare key
of station and Janek have the key?
You just do not think about that?
-And you?
Sorry, I had another thing in my head
.
I examined the creature.
Maybe you could contribute a part.
Really?
Falk , not now.
We have to do only what is important
and not waste more time.
Move.
Please.
This would be easier if you had your own key
.
Bitch.
Do not move. Do not move.
All right, kid.
Hey, how are you?
Come on.
Harald told you what's going on?
Tinni.
He knows me yet.
Course.
He really missed you.
He still did not understand.
Because you went away suddenly.
Here, look at this.
What is this?
Janek, I was pregnant.
My Age?
Course.
E?
This is a joke, right?
What's next?
Aliens?
I understand this correctly?
Wanted to hide the fact that
had found these animals, these mutants?
We were concerned about public safety.
We did not want to cause panic.
We were not sure of the risk.
Said they were attacked by a bird, right?
Maybe this has absolutely nothing to do. Yes
Maybe it was just a bird of prey,
who attacked randomly.
Just attacked randomly
only a bird of prey?
What bird has a stinger?
Leave me alone.
Idiot.
Since when raptors
attack people? This is a legend.
They are noble animals.
Bertl, do me a favor, please
do not open your mouth unless you ask.
Open the door.
Janek, what's the plan now?
I find Birte and Falk.
Janek, no. You have no idea where they are
. Are probably already dead.
So I will get the satellite phone.
Janek, this is crazy.
Leave me alone.
What is this?
Abram.
Close the door.
Falk? Falk, where the
satellite phone?
With Birte.
I was Birte.
With Birte?
Where is she?
I do not know.
She fled. When the hybrid
attacked us.
Stop. Stop.
Go away.
He was.
I think it was.
Please make it stop.
Make it stop.
Wait, I'm going.
I'll get the drill.
The  end of days.
Centuries working and is now here.
The gates of hell have opened.
How was the Bible.
And the way we open
.
We lost our way.
We're dead.
Let die.
I lost my way.
I wanted it.
I never imagined this.
Stop this idiocy now.
Tanja, when the helicopter
must come pick us up?
Noon tomorrow, if not
hear no contact us.
Okay.
When they see that we are not there and that
had no message from us,
will think that something happened to me.
I think it will take three to four hours until
send someone down here.
Tomorrow . Tomorrow night will probably
get here.
If we can keep ourselves safe until
there, so let's do this.
Definitely will come sooner.
Urs was the valley and
will help.
Yes, you're right.
Will come sooner.
But those who will come looking for you
do not know what is happening.
'll Be a mountain rescue team
Normal, completely unarmed.
It will be a disaster.
Will not hear from Luca,
will send a team of armed guards.
This is not good. The girl will not hold out until tomorrow
.
Had septicemia.
Will fall into a coma soon.
Need the satellite phone.
I'm going to the station.
Well I'll go with you.
No, you stay here.
-Why?
You are too old.
Just let her go.
Listen to reason.
I'm going with you.
And you will too.
I'm not leaving.
Yes, you will.
Do not know if you told the truth.
Maybe Birte is elsewhere.
You'll help us find her.
Come on. Come on.
I've been through this before.
Have you?
All this?
Interesting. And how it ended?
Septicemia, I mean. We had to carry one in
Pazuzu.
Yes Yes
How will this help her?
Calm. It's okay.
What's wrong with her?
Only pain.
You.
Hey you.
You have painkillers here?
Acorda. Analgesics.
No, I think not.
But I'll check again, ok?
I think she's waking up.
Help us. Fast.
Calm down.
's Okay. Help is on the way.
Do you hear me? Calm.
I think she heard me.
's Okay. It's okay.
You'll be fine.
What? What happened?
What?
Oh, my God.
What is this?
It may be that the girl was infected by bird
.
And now a mutation is developing.
We have to take it out, right?
Open the door. This can not be born here
.
She's right .
Will not help anything if born here, right?
E will help in that it
born out there, huh?
You do not have enough out there?
Damn these birds with stingers
mutants?
I also do not want the girl
die.
And what do you suggest?
Let's burn.
What?
Cut out and burn.
Scissors.
Tongs, please.
Okay.
Put this on the fire.
Hot iron, now.
She has a pulse?
Okay. Now we sew
it fast.
At least here we have a clear vision.
Here we can see what is coming.
Do you really think the
girl has a chance?
Course.
If we go fast enough.
I hope we find the phone.
I hope it is not broken.
Why do you care?
What?
If the girl dies or not.
Fuck you.
One less person to drive the car,
breathe, and cause holes in the air.
Shut up.
And after all, is not much better for her to die?
Do not need to see the end of the world.
How old is she? 17? 18?
Hey, it's never too late to abort
.
Shut up. Stop.
Stop it now.
Shut up.
What's wrong?
That was the biggest mistake of my life.
Where you think you're going?
Let's get together, ok?
Good
Not bad, huh?
Not bad.
But now I could drink.
Wait,
I believe still has a bottle of rum here.
I'll bring cups.
After all, the scenery here is absolutely amazing
.
But next time I will
traveling somewhere else.
Hello Let me join.
Open the door. Fast.
Oh, God. Urs.
Help me.
Mr. Krakauer, please help me.
-Listen, we have to treat it.
Listen, we'll help you.
Relief. A doctor I need a doctor
. Please.
Stay here.
Birte.
Call her.
Birte? Are you there?
Go inside.
Between.
Nothing without
Birte and without satellite phone.
E?
-Nothing.
Now?
I do not know where she was.
Come on.
Come on up.
Move.
Birte?
What is this?
Come on.
Birte?
Should be under it.
Slow. Care.
Oh, God.
What happened there, Falk?
What?
Give me the gun.
Falk.
Shut up.
Put there.
Come on.
Is urgent. We need a helicopter
rescue station for research Glazius.
Evacuation of seven.
One of them is seriously injured.
About 20 years probably
septicemia. Quickly.
Janek.
It's the season.
-Here, take the phone. Come on.
What do we do now?
Tanja.
Where is the girl?
Janek  come. Come on.
Do not do that.
Do not.
Translation and sync: saredes
scarytorrent.com.br